Hey, uh, I just found out I have to be
at the telescope lab all weekend.
(Raj:)Any chance you and Bernadette
could take care of my dog?
- Why don't you put her in a kennel?
- Why don't you put your mother in a home?
(Howard:)To be honest, she'd do better in the kennel.
(Howard:)- I'll talk to Bernie. I'm sure it's fine.
- Thank you.
(Sheldon:)It's happening. Leonard, it's happening.
(Sheldon:)Professor Proton is coming to our house.
(Leonard:)You're kidding.
(Howard:)You mean the guy who used to host
that lame kids show?
(Sheldon:)And you just got yourself uninvited.
See, I told you I'd find a tactful way
to do that.
- How'd you get him to come to your house?
- As Professor Proton always says:
"There is no problem you can't solve
if you use your noggin."
- And he wrote him a check.
- Yeah, that too. Big check.
(Raj:)Uncle Howard.